Women's Building; Records apap292
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative File, 1971-2000, Undated; 1; 10 cubic ft.
  - Bills - W. I Hart Locksmith, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Bills - Lawyers, Walterthay & Long, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Bills - Nancy Machold, Fundraising Consultant, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Bills - Niagara Mohawk, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - Bills - NYS Disabling Benefits, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Bills - New York Telephone, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Bills - Office Price Printing, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Bills, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Bills - Property Taxes, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Bills - Receipts, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Bills - Schatz, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Bills - Taub Heating & Plumbing Inc., 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Bills - U.S. Postal Service, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Bills - Vacarelli, Michael E - Printer, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Budget and Committee Structure, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Capital Campaign, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Capital Campaign, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Bills - Women Make Movies, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Bills - Workers Compensation and Disability, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Capital Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Capital Campaign - Construction, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Capital Campaign - Events, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Capital Campaign - Feasibility Study, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Capital Campaign - Holding Our Own, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Capital Campaign - Honorary Committee - Gloria DeSole, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Capital Campaign - Ro Rosen, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Capital Campaign - Honorary Committee - Maria Semedei - Otero, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Capital Campaign - Individual Giving, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Capital Campaign - Notes, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Capital Campaign - Plans, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Capital Campaign - programming, survey/costs, purchases, rehabilitation, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Capital Campaign - Public Relations, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Capital Campaign - Telemack Resources, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Capital Campaign " The Women's Building a Brief History ", 1987; 1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Capital Repertory Company Benefit, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Committee Lists, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Community Outreach, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Corporate/ Found, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - "Dream Come to Reality", 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Elevator Proposal - Department of Housing and Community Development Grant, 1987; 1991 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Emergency - Police, etc., 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - End of Year Financial Reports, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Financial Statements & Grants Applications, 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - General Contractor, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - Historical, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Historical, 1987-1991 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Holding Our Own Agreement, ca.1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 60)
  - Holding Our Own Report, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 61)
  - Income Receipts - Rents Received, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 62)
  - Energy, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 63)
  - Lease, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 64)
  - Junior League Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 65)
  - Frederick McDonald Foundation Trust, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 66)
  - Membership, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 67)
  - Membership List, ca.1980 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 68)
  - New Building, 1987; 1989; 1990 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 69)
  - New Building Documents "For the Record", 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 70)
  - Non - Profits Officemates, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 71)
  - Other Women's Buildings, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 72)
  - Personnel, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative File), Folder 73)
  - Report on Women's Building - Holding Our Own, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Statement of Unity, ca.1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Study of Existing Building Proposal Work, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Survey of Potential Tenant, 1987; 1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Tax Exemption Certification, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Transition Miscellaneous Material - Capital Campaign Committee Interviews, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Transition Miscellaneous Material - Mailing for Capital Campaign Committee Grant, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Transition Team Reports HOO Project, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Transition Team Reports, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Astraea Found Proposal, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Capital Campaign, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Capital Campaign - 20 most Frequently asked Questions, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Capital Campaign - Committee Structure, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Capital Campaign - Campaign Progress, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Capital Campaign - Committees Mailing Lists, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Capital Campaign - Donor Acknowledgments, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Capital Campaign, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Capital Campaign - Winnie DeLoayza, 1988; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Capital Campaign - Winnie DeLoayza, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Capital Campaign Drive, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Capital Campaign - Events, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Capital Campaign - Executive Summary, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Capital Campaign - First Annual "Women Make History Work", 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Capital Campaign for Government Funding, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Capital Campaign - Grassroots, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Capital Campaign - Holding Our Own Loan, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Capital Campaign - Hudson Mohawk, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Capital Campaign - Hudson Mohawk, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Capital Campaign - Open House Guest Book, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Capital Campaign - Products Listing, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Capital Campaign - Products Material Sent Out, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Capital Campaign - Records, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Capital Campaign - Roles and Responsibilities, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Capital Campaign - Schedule of Gifts, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Capital Campaign - Steps in Selling, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Capital Campaign - Steps Selling, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Capital Campaign Tenants, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Capital Campaign - Transition Team Manager, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Capital Campaign - Workers, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Capital Campaign - Work Plan, ca.1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Change Orders - Building Construction, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Committees, 1988-1992 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Committees/ Task Forces, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Coordinating Council, 1988-1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - Donated Building Supplies, 1988; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - Elevator Proposal - Member Item, Paul Tonko Disputo, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 4 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Federal Tax Report - Form 990, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Finance, 1988-1993 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Finance - First Albany Corporation, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Finance - Prudential - Bache, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Fundraising, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Junior League of Albany - Grant Application, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes - Coordinating Council, 1988-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes - Coordinating Council, 1988-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Newsletter Advertisements, 1988; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes - Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - Physical Building, 1988; 1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Pre - Campaign - Winnie DeLoayza, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Program Task Force, Membership Discount Coupons - Michelle Crone, 1988; 1992; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Promotional, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Sidewalk Damage, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Sub-Contractors, ca.1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - Supporter's Lottery, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Taxes, 1988-1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Thank Yous for Donations to WB, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Annual Membership Meeting, 1989; 1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Artists in Building, 1989; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Capital Campaign, ca.1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989-1990; 1993-1994 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Capital Campaign List, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Checking Journal Pages, 1989; 1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Alexandra Douglas Holding Our Own Agreement Draft, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Federal Tax Report - Form 990, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Federal Campaign Contract, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Fiscal Year, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Fundraising(loose), 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Grand Opening - Promotion, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Kirsh Foundation, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Membership, 1989; 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Membership, 1989-1993 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Outreach Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Progress Report and Annual Operating Budget, 1987; 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Public Relations, 1989; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Nominations, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Rotary Club, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Thank You, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - WMHT (Radio), 1989; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Women's Building Advertisements, 1989-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Annual Meeting Returns, 1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Building use Log, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - By-Laws, 1990; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Combined Federal Appeal, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Coordinating Council Board Manual - Financial Statements, 1990-1993 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Correspondence from St. rose concerning space rental for auction, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Donors, ca.1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Elevator Grant Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Federal Tax Report - Form 990, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Finance Committee, 1990; 1995 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Grant Information, elevator, fundraising, 1990-1991; 1996 (Box 5 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Hiring Office, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Holding Our Own, 1990-1991; 1995-1996 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Housing Ads - Outdated, 1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Insurance - New York, Casualty Policy Changes, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Liability Releases, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Newsletter Volunteers, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Potential Donors, 1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Thank Yous sent, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Advertising Letters, 1991; 1995-1996 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Council, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Form 990, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee, 1991 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Major Donor Campaign, 1991; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Major Donor Campaign, 1991; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Major Donor Campaign, 1991; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - Membership, 1991 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Membership Committee - Survey, 1991 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Personnel Policies and Benefits, 1991 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - T-Shirts, 1991; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Advertising, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Community Development Block Grant Report, 1992-1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Community Development Block Grant Report, 1992-1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Community Development Block Grant Report, 1992-1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Finance - Auction Program Booklet, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Form 990, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Grant Information, general, 1992-1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Gail Dieten - Tax Records and Financial Statements, 1992; 1995-1999 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Grants, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Hewlett - Packard Grant received, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Newsletter - Summer, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Participation Figures, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Payroll, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Volunteers, 1992; 1996; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Advertising: Blues Concert, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Advertising information and listings, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Budget, Elevator Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Direct Mail, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Donors - Individual, 1993; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Form 990 - Fiscal Year, 1993-1994 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Grant Information, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Newsletter Minutes, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Newsletter Committee, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - SEFA, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - SEFA ad, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - SEFA - United Way Donations, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Women's Organization Directory, 1993; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Accounts Payable - WEQX, 1994-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Artwork Donated/ Loaned, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Capital District Arts Decentralization Program, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Coalition for Donor Choice, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Direct Mail - Women's Building News, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - IOLA Grant, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Individual Major Donors, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Potential Adventures, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Referral Logs, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - SEFA Campaign, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Tides Foundation Agreement, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - United Way of Schenectady, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Women's Center Conference, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Women's Directory - changes, 1994; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Accounts Payable, 1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Accounts Payable - Quick Books, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Accounts payable - Receipts and Invoices, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Accounts Payable - U.S. Postal Service Permit Account, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Accounts Payable - Working Assets, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Advertising - oneshots, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Advertising, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Advertising, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Advertising - Brochure Original copy, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Budget/Financial, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Building Feasibility Committee, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 60)
  - Building Feasibility Committee/ Retail Space, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 61)
  - Calendar, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 62)
  - Checkbooks, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 63)
  - Committee, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 64)
  - Community Foundation, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 65)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting (financial crisis), 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 66)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 67)
  - Coordinating Council Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 68)
  - Cultural Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 69)